P'Dan.
Let's break up.
I knew
that you didn't like me.
Thank you so much.
Can we talk for a minute?
I want to know everything you do.
Jane. Hey.
Hey.
Hey!
I'll cover you.
If I don't make it back within ten minutes,
just drive away.
P'Jane!
Jane's always dragging people
into things like this.
If you're worried about him,
please help talk some sense into him.
He probably won't listen to me.
I don't think he'd listen to me either.
I wish you nothing but luck.
So, you're not going to quit, right?
If you choose this kind of life,
I wish you the best of luck then.
What are you doing?
Please go back and sit down first.
Jane, you can't just abandon me like this.
Have you forgotten?
That you owe me.
Please go back and sit down first.
We can talk later.
Go back and wait for me at the condo first.
I'll follow you there shortly.
Can you even make it back by yourself?
I'll have my driver pick me up.
Wait for me at the condo.
I'm never letting you go.
You walk in with a warning sign
Just one look and already falling for you
My friends tell me not to cross that line
But I’m already out of time
I know the truth, I taste the sin
It’s wrong but I don’t want it to be true
I’m losing all my discipline
You’re all I’m thinking of
and I’m breaking all the rules
just because…
You’re a red flag but I’m colorblind
I know you’re dangerous
If it burns, let it burn me alive
I can't hold myself back, I’d cross every line
Ooh
Stay still.
I'll do it for you.
I can do it.
I've done it before.
You're being stubborn again.
That's enough.
Come here.
Thank you
for not leaving me.
Are you still worried about something?
Are you afraid that staying with me
will put you in danger?
Don't worry.
I won't let anyone lay a finger on you.
And if you're worried
about anything happening to me,
I don't die easily.
I can trust you, right?
If anything happens to you,
I don't think I can go on.
Ugh, I'm so damn sleepy.
Why the hell aren't there any night classes?
By the way, where the hell did Jane disappear to?
Hey,
aren't finals coming up soon?
I can't get ahold of him at all.
Yeah, actually, I haven't seen him either.
Is he sick or something?
I have no idea.
Do you know anything, Put?
Nope.
Shit.
Damn it.
I'm worried about him,
afraid he's gonna miss the exams.
Worry about yourself first, man.
Oh, I'll take the exams for sure.
But whether I'll pass is a different story.
Hello, Uncle.
Hi.
Hi there, are you looking for Jane?
Yes, sir.
Jane's not home.
Do you know where he went, Uncle?
I don't know, he didn't say.
But I saw him
grab quite a few bags of medicine.
I see.
Thank you very much, see you around.
Alright, alright, bye.
Hmm?
I brewed some herbal medicine for you.
Thank you.
Drink it slowly, it's hot.
Where have you been?
Why aren't you resting?
Your stitches might rip open.
You promised me, right?
That you'd tell me everything.
It's just business
you know that.
Let me go change my clothes first.
Then I'm going to see my friends tonight.
Since you can still go off and do your business.
Hello?
What are you up to?
Nothing much.
Are you free tonight?
I'm kinda stressed out.
You wanna get drunk?
I have some booze.
Sure.
I remember.
Back in freshman year
when we went to China together, right?
That day, my phone
counted like twenty thousand steps.
But on that day,
you and I went back to the hotel first.
But do you remember?
Gap walked nearly thirty thousand steps.
Really?
Like...
Oh.
Gap went shopping afterwards.
Or to be exact, the bastard
followed Cherry around to carry her shopping bags.
When he got back to the hotel,
he was like this
I can't take this anymore.
Gap, Gap.
It's okay.
For Cherry,
this is a piece of cake.
Hey,
honestly, I think Cherry can tell.
He's got a shot, though.
Going after her like that
If he still not her boyfriend by graduation,
he should just give up.
True.
But seriously, going to China back then was
so much fun.
On the day we had to return,
I didn't want to come back at all.
If we could travel like that forever,
that'd be nice, right?
Look at you,
getting all emotional again.
Shit,
calling me out.
But I like it,
you being like this.
Come on, cheers.
So,
what exactly happened
during the time you went missing?
I almost died.
What?
I...
almost got shot.
But I'm okay.
It's because of P'Jane, right?
Why
does he have to drag you into dangerous,
fucked-up shit like that?
It's not his fault.
I was the one who asked him to take me along.
You asked him?
Well, if I'm going to spend my life with him,
I want to know
what kind of life he lives.
Now that you know, how is it?
I don't think I can handle it.
He's driving me absolutely insane.
You can get out of there, you know.
Out of his life.
You're afraid
he'll come after you to take you back, right?
If there's anything I can do to help,
just tell us.
This time, I'll protect you myself.
I can't get out.
Yes, you can.
If we work together, there has to be a way.
You just don't understand.
I love him so much
that I can't bring myself to leave him.
But staying with him,
I'm also terrified
that one day I'll see something happen to him.
So, why did you come see me then?
I don't know.
I just couldn't keep this to myself anymore.
And you're
the only friend who knows everything.
Why?
Hey,
what the hell are you doing?
Even though whenever anyone
asks you for anything,
you do absolutely everything for them.
But when it comes to me,
I ask you for just one thing,
and you can't do it for me.
Put, calm down.
At least,
just this once.
Put, what's wrong with you?
Can you please just do what I ask for once?
Put, it hurts.
Let go!
Jane.
You're wasted right now!
Hey!
What the hell is wrong with you, Put!
Jane.
You piece of shit, Put.
Hey.
Jane.
Let go.
Jane. Let go.
Jane.
Let go!
Ow!
Jane, I'm sorry.
I think you should just stop.
I understand you.
It's my fault.
Shit.
I shouldn't have done that.
It's my fault.
It's all because of me.
It's because of me.
Forget it.
I'm leaving.
Jane.
How did you get here?
Jane,
I'm really sorry about just now.
Argh!
Hey!
P'Jane!
It's not what you think!
Stop!
P'Jane!
Enough!
If you don't stop,
I'm never going to see you again.
If you ever come near Jane again,
I won't let you off easy.
We shouldn't see each other for a while, Put.
How did you know where I was?
Huh?
Why aren't you answering?
How do you always know where I am?
Do you have a spy here,
or did you secretly put a tracker on me?
Jane, calm down first.
Stop tracking me already!
I'm just afraid you won't be safe.
So,
do I have to thank you for this?
Do you even know that what you're doing is
toxic as hell?
Jane...
Everything you think is good,
both the favor
and the tracking..
Have you ever even tried to
understand anyone else?
The wound was almost healed.
Then why did it tear open even more?
Huh?
What did you do?
And how is your boyfriend doing?
Why do you even want to know?
I know
that whatever I say,
I can't order you around anyway.
But you should stop living your life like this.
Is my life really that hard to understand?
It's not normal!
But I chose this path myself.
You know how I grew up.
I understand,
but others don't, do they?
Right?
Do you even realize that
on the day you got shot,
your boyfriend was worried sick about you?
If you don't care about yourself,
at least care about the people who love you.
Hey.
What are you doing?
Working.
P'Jane...
I'm not in the mood.
Please, can you not?
I'm really not in the mood right now.
This weekend, I'd like to go back
and stay with my family.
Of course.
Jane,
are you asleep yet?
What is it?
There's something I want to ask.
I want to know,
when we first agreed to date,
what kind of life together did you imagine?
I never liked anything flashy.
Do you know
that my happiest day
wasn't the day you closed down a whole restaurant
to surprise me for Valentine's Day.
Then which day was it?
It was the day you went to see my family
to prove
that you were sincere about me.
That day,
you tried to help me with everything.
You were so clumsy, you know.
I felt like
I was one of the very few people
who got to see that side of you.
The side where you weren't some superhero,
or a demon
that people rumored you to be.
Do you like seeing me like that?
Just having ordinary days together,
having times where we can laugh.
But I also know
that you don't want that kind of life.
So I realized...
maybe we're just too different.
Go to sleep.
(Thanapat Piboonosot)
Oh, Jane,
you're back just in time.
Great,
we can all have dinner together.
Is there anything special you want to eat?
Anything is fine.
Is something wrong
with him?
Yeah, I wonder.
Want some stir-fried veggies?
Eat up, eat a lot.
Ah..
No more, I can't finish it all.
Want an omelet?
I can fry one up for you.
Uh,
and...
didn't your boyfriend drop you off today?
Huh?
Why did you ask that?
I'm full.
Hey...
Do you have any idea how worried I was?
Can you please stop living your life like this?
I can't stop.
I've come too far to turn back.
It's my life.
How do you think I can bear it?
Having to see you live
like this every single day.
That's exactly why I didn't want to
involve you in any of this.
If you choose this kind of life,
I wish you the best of luck then.
Hi P'Put.
Hello.
What are you doing here?
Is Jane home.
He's not.
Ah ok, thanks.
Sure.
(Put: I'm really sorry about that day.)
Hi.
Today, we're going to show you
how to make ginkgo nuts in syrup.
There are only a few ingredients.
Brown sugar, pandan leaves,
and boiled ginkgo nuts.
We will bring the water to a boil.
Once the water is boiling,
we will add the brown sugar.
And most importantly,
pandan leaves to add a nice aroma.
When the sugar dissolves,
we will add the boiled ginkgo nuts.
After that,
we'll let it simmer for about five minutes.
We can put the lid on and wait.
Here it is, our ginkgo nuts in syrup.
Be sure to give this recipe a try.
(Caption: Or maybe we're just too different)
(Gap)
Hello?
Hello, Jane?
Get to the hospital right now.
Put is in the ER room right now.
He's in critical condition.
Yeah, I'll be right there.
What happened to Put?
Well...
Put was riding his big bike,
and a speeding car swerved
into his lane and hit him.
They said it looked like a luxury car.
Must be some rich kid for sure.
The bastard even did a hit-and-run.
They can't track them down.
And...
Put's family went to work out of town,
but I've called and told them all.
They're on their way and should be here soon.
Who is Jenalee?
I am.
The patient asked to see you.
The patient is still conscious right now,
but it might not be for much longer.
This way, please.
Right this way.
Put...
Hang in there a bit longer.
Your family is on their way.
I'm...
sorry.
P'...
Jane.
What did you say?
P'Jane...
What about P'Jane, Put?
Put...
What about P'Jane?
Put!
Doctor!
Doctor, please help him!
Please wait outside.
Put!
Put...
Jane,
how is he, sweetie?
Auntie...
Jane, you went in to see Put, right?
How is he? Huh?
How is he doing?
Auntie...
Put... he's... not with us anymore
It's not true, right?
It's not true.
I don't believe it.
Is it really true?
No way.
When I went inside,
I didn't know what to say to him.
I didn't even get to say
a proper goodbye to him yet.
Why did it happen so fast?
You guys just made up not too long ago.
Jane...
I'm really sorry about just now.
Argh! Hey!
If you ever come near Jane again,
I won't let you off easy.
It's not true! It's not true!
Jane?
Okay.
You did a great job.
You got all the evidence clean, right?
Then our favor is now concluded.
Pleasure doing business with you.
Jane, what are you doing?
Why are you doing this?
You killed Put, didn't you?
Did you kill him?
What happened?
Put is dead?
I know nothing about this.
How can I trust you?
How many times have you lied to me before?
Besides,
before he died,
Put said your name.
And on that day, you went and threatened him.
If you don't believe me,
you can go tell the police.
I'm more than willing to
let them fully investigate me.
What can the police even do to someone like you?
Jane...
Can you please trust me just this once?
Trust you?
I can't handle this anymore.
I can't handle this anymore, damn it!
Do you hear me?
I can't handle this anymore!
I can't trust you anymore!
Ever since you came into my life,
everything has been completely ruined.
I have nothing left, P'Jane.
Jane...
You're the person who gives anyone
whatever they ask for, right?
Then I'm asking you to disappear from my life.
Are you fully in your right mind right now?
Are you really insisting
on making a contract with me?
A contract where I can demand anything back
from you in return.
Yes.
Then tonight,
I ask to stay with you for one last night.
And after this,
I will disappear from your life.
And we won't owe each other
anything anymore, right?
If that's what you want.
Hello, Jane.
I'm sorry for leaving without saying goodbye.
But I didn't think I'd be strong enough
to walk out of your life
if you were still awake.
The reason I had to leave this letter behind
is because there's something
I absolutely have to tell you.
But I'm not good with words,
which is why I have to write it down like this.
The reason I chose to leave you
isn't because I killed Put.
I didn't do it.
If you won't believe me,
I understand,
because everything I've done to you has been awful.
And that is exactly
the reason why I'm leaving you.
I want you to be able to smile
again like the old Jane,
the one before you ever knew me.
You might not trust me anymore,
but there is one thing I want to reassure you
I have never once lied to you.
The part where I told you
that you are special to me.
You often think of yourself as ordinary,
But you are is the most extraordinary
ordinary person in the world to me.
So, I want to tell you ten reasons
that make me think you are so very special.
First,
everyone who knows me
either wants something from me
or looks at me like a demon.
But just looking into your eyes,
I knew you were the first person
who didn't judge me from our very first meeting.
Second,
the way you get nervous
when dancing with me is so cute.
No matter how many dozens of times
you step on my feet,
I don't mind.
Third,
you changed my mind about a lot of things.
You made me believe that this world
still has people who want to strive
and do things on their own.
Fourth,
I never liked taking photos,
but you made me willing to
take photos with you.
I wanted to have photos of us together,
wanted to declare that you belong to me alone.
Fifth,
I don't care how anyone else looks at me,
except for you.
You were willing to fight with your friends for me,
so I wanted to prove myself
to you and your family.
Sixth,
you said I make you happy
when we're together.
I'm happy when I'm with you too.
Seventh,
you made me realize that
things made from the heart
are much more important than
countless luxury items.
So I wanted to make something simple
but made from the heart for you to eat.
Eighth,
you worry about me and take care of me,
both by bringing me Chinese medicine
and helping tend to my wounds.
Ninth,
you were willing to step into my world,
even though it was painful.
In the past, I dragged you into my life,
but I never tried to step into yours.
So I fully intended to try and learn,
and I was determined to do it.
But I guess I started too late.
Last reason,
I once told you that the rule of being together
is that you shouldn't be too emotional.
But actually, you being emotional
is a good thing,
I just wanted to see you become a bit stronger.
You've never been selfish at all.
You always ask for everything
for the sake of others.
I'm the only one who has been selfish,
back when we made our contract
and I asked for you to belong to me alone.
In reality, I was just afraid of losing you,
but I really didn't know what to do.
So I used the method that used to work.
I'm sorry, Jane.
I know it wasn't right.
And the thing I'm going to do for you
is to willingly step out of your life.
I won't ever come back to this condo again.
But whenever you miss this place,
you already have the keycard.
You can always come here, okay?
Love you with all my heart.
Big Jane belongs to Little Jane.
When you said you loved me,
or were you just saying it?
Because what you did makes it so clear
You tricked me into loving you,
and then you destroyed me
You said you loved me,
yet you hurt me
The more I love you,
the more it hurts
I just want to know,
did you ever love me?
Did you ever love me?
Ooh
I just want to know,
did you ever love me?
I thought your love was real
So I gave you everything
But you went and ruined it all
You made me feel like I was important
Made me believe that I was special,
Hmm
But none of it was true
In the end, it was just me who fell for you
Having to cry over the trust I gave
When you said you loved me,
or were you just saying it?
Because what you did makes it so clear
You tricked me into loving you,
and then you destroyed me
You said you loved me,
yet you hurt me
The more I love you,
the more it hurts
I just want to know,
did you ever love me?
If I could turn back time
To the days before you,
I’d choose to start over
There is no way I would ever fall for you again
In the end, it was just me who fell for you
Having to cry over the trust I gave
When you said you loved me,
or were you just saying it?
Because what you did makes it so clear
You tricked me into loving you,
and then you destroyed me
You said you loved me,
yet you hurt me
The more I love you,
the more it hurts
I just want to know,
did you ever love me?
Ooh,
all this time, did you ever love me at all?
Did you love me?
Ooh
When you said you loved me,
or were you just saying it?
Because what you did makes it so clear